<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MapIt</string>
   
<string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
<string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    
    <string name="about_txt">A map is a visual representation of an area – symbolic depiction highlighting relationships between elements of that space such as objects, regions, and themes.\n\nMany maps are static two-dimensional, geometrically accurate (or approximately accurate) representations of three-dimensional space, while others are dynamic or interactive, even three-dimensional. Although most commonly used to depict geography, maps may represent any space, real or imagined, without regard to context or scale; e.g. brain mapping, DNA mapping and extraterrestrial mapping.\n\nAlthough the earliest maps known are of the heavens, geographic maps of territory have a very long tradition and exist from ancient times. The word "map" comes from the medieval Latin Mappa mundi, wherein mappa meant napkin or cloth and mundi the world. Thus, "map" became the shortened term referring to a two-dimensional representation of the surface of the world.\n\n\nThe orientation of a map is the relationship between the directions on the map and the corresponding compass directions in reality. The word "orient" is derived from Latin oriens, meaning East. In the Middle Ages many maps, including the T and O maps, were drawn with East at the top (meaning that the direction "up" on the map corresponds to East on the compass).</string>
    <string name="get_me_some">Get Me Somewhere</string>
    <string name="my_home">My Home</string>
    <string name="my_work_place">My Work Places</string>
    <string name="saved_places">Saved Places</string>
    <string name="pls_sel_city">Please select a city</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="end">End</string>
    <string name="get_route">Get Route</string>
    <string name="enter_address">Enter address...</string>
    <string name="leaving">Leaving</string>
    <string name="set_arrival">Set arrival time</string>
    <string name="degree_cel">\u2103</string>
    <string name="notify_near_bus">Notify when nearing a bus stop</string>

</resources>